[{"answer": "Nobody wants to say that there's been a rape in their command.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 1, "question": "Is this the U.S. military's dirty secret?", "qSentId": 0}, {"answer": "In the last report by the Sexual Assault Prevention Response Office in fiscal year 2009, over 3,000 -- 3,230 sexual assaults were reported throughout DOD, all the four branches.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "How many cases are we seeing per year and is it getting worse?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, the case has been brought by Berk Peel LLC, a law firm in Washington, D.C. and we're -- sort of spokesman and consultant for the suit.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Why have you taken that step and do you think you can be successful?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, it is a very hyper masculine culture and I did a predominantly male job.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "What was happening to you before you got raped?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "My first reaction was I just want to go home.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "What did you do?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Right, I was administratively discharged and I spent five years after my discharge fighting with the Department of Defense to get my record corrected and five years after my discharge in 2005 I was finally awarded a medical retirement.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "So Myla, in essence, you end up getting sexually abused and raped and you then get thrown out of the military, and this is after nine years of great service to your country?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Is that one of the main reasons that you didn't pursue this and didn't report it?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Yes, about a year later, I had gotten out of the army and moved to Fort Leonard Wood, Missouri, and I ran into the guy that raped me and went into a little bit of shock and requested to speak to a sexual assault response coordinator or to a chaplain.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And Rebekah, you actually went to one of the army chaplains who gave you some extraordinary advice, didn't he?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Completely, and it's even worse in job fields that tend to be male dominated.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Which is really unacceptable?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I would say that it is very much a command accountability issue and institutionally the military is sexist but most of the workplaces that I worked in when I was in the Army, the leadership had zero tolerance for any sexual harassment so in the workplaces in which the command did not support that atmosphere I didn't have any problems.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "And what would you say, Myla?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, I think sexism is allowed to exist generally in the military but the larger problem with sexual abuse in the military is there's no institutional accountability.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Or is that an unfair labeling really of the situation?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, at the time that I was approached by the investigator to give a statement, I already knew at that time that giving a statement would end my career in CID.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What happened when this all became a public matter for you?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, several of my good friends really stood by me throughout this ordeal.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Yes, but did everybody ostracize you or were there any Good Samaritan types who came forward to offer you protection?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I did not, and I did not because I chose to use a restricted reporting option and that's exactly why I chose to use that option because I knew if I started an investigation that there would be the ostracism -- the criticism.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Did you have the same experience as Myla?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "The restricted reporting option is an option in which a victim can report the crime to only certain individuals including medical personnel and the necessary evidence will be collected and then the victim can maintain some level of confidentiality, but they are actually ordered not to talk to anybody else about it, not even friends.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Myla, the option that Rebekah is talking about, what is that exactly and why didn't you take it?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, of course, I mean there are lots of positives.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "What is the situation?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Did you see any abuse when you were serving?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "I actually don't regret joining the military at all.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "And do you remain proud of your service in the military?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I don't regret it, but I don't think that I would do it again.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Rebekah, how about you?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, we'll se what happens with the lawsuit.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "What happens?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I would encourage any young woman or man to follow his or her dreams and to join the military if that's what they want to do.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What would your message be to any young woman watching this who has been interested in pursuing a career in the military, but is now horrified at what she's hearing?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "-- \"America's Got Talent\" obviously.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Second?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "You know, I feel relief.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "How do you feel now it's all out in the open?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "I was five years old.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "How old were you at the time?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Then he would touch me inappropriately and I knew it was inappropriate.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Then what happened?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Even at the age -- I just felt uncomfortable.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Even at the age of five?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Classic pedophile behavior, isn't it?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I couldn't.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "At the time, did you tell your mother or your stepfather anything about it?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I -- what I remember -- because it's such a foggy memory since I was just five years old, I just remember them in shock and then the next thing I remember is I'm testifying against him in court at age six.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What was your mother's reaction, in particular, when you said to her that you had also been through this?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I can just remember the feeling I felt.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "ORGAN: Can you remember much of that?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Sometimes I feel like both of them feel guilty.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "That she left you with this guy?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think a lot, growing up with no self-esteem, no confidence, getting into abusive relationships in high school with men, not knowing my boundaries, feeling like I always need to please and have no self-respect for who I am.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What's been the impact to you psychologically, do you think?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Quiet.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What kind of child were you before that happened, do you think?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Because I was scared to be alone.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Why did you do that?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "When -- you know when he came back and he was upset, I felt like I couldn't leave.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "He keeps spinning you the same old story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "URKE: My dancing, just being called from New York, a great -- a great opportunity for me here happened.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What made you finally do it?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Never looked back.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "And never looked back?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I think I'm still healing and I'm a work in progress, for sure.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How are you now, do you think, psychologically?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Not so much meltdowns.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Do you have bad days, when you just lose it because of all that's happened to you?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I have a hard time trusting men.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Do you -- do you trust men?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "But I can imagine every one that comes up to you, particularly if you're famous, it's even more difficult to get any kind of trust going, isn't it?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean put -- putting yourself -- I was put on blast for my weight.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "-- and people poking fun at you?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "No, I don't think I'm fat.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "So when you look at yourself there, what do you think?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "It is dangerous.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "I mean, this is dangerous stuff, isn't it?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I would say thank God I testified against you.", "docId": "110216pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What would you say to the old man who took away your innocence?", "qSentId": 486}]